(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-14T09:03:48.311168",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Say ho!
ho!
Say yo!
yo!
よっしゃみんなで掛け声いくぞ！ワン、ツー、ワンツースリーの！
Alright everyone, let's do the call and response! One, two, one-two-three, go!
そんなところもかわ世！！
Even that side of you is so cute!!
みなよん感づいて来い来い
Everyone, catch on and come here!
たまにぼーとしたおいおい
Sometimes spacing out, hey hey!
先は歌えばよやよや
Ahead, if you sing, yaya!
この道を進むのだん
We march onward down this path!
あれもね疲れちゃうなゆっくりと歩みましょ
But getting tired is no fun, let's walk it slowly.
人生なんて気楽に構えましょ
Let's take life easy and relax.
なんて言ってたらちゃんと知ろって
If I say that, you better know properly—
どっち？どっちどっち？
Which? Which one, which one?
どっちの君も大正解！
Either version of you is totally correct!
だってこの世はめちゃかわ世！
Because this world is super cute!
ダメなとこもかわ世！
Even your flaws make you so cute!
生まれてくれてありがとね
Thank you for being born into this world.
みんな大だいだいだいすきを百回！！
I love you a hundred times over!
ねえねえそんなこんよはかわよ
Hey hey, is such a night cute...
手合いもくれる君かわよ！
You giving me your hand is so cute!
ラブこそマソソニラブだから
Because love is the ultimate, pure love!
あまりあるかわのよつくりましょ
Let's create an abundance of cuteness!
あまり振り回しすぎたらもしやしてあきらめられちゃうかな
If we swing things around too much, might you give up on me?
懲りずにね愛してほしいな
Without getting tired of it, I want you to love me.
そんなところもかわ世！！
Even that side of you is so cute!!
失敗は気にしないでんない
Don't worry about mistakes at all!
ちょっと心配になってきた
I'm getting a little worried.
日々は夢かける勝ち抜けのレズ
Days are a race to chase dreams and win through!
本日もお仕事がんばりましょう
Let's do our best at work today too!
でもな自分のペースでまったりもしたいしな
But you know, I also want to take things at my own pace.
どっちどっちどっち？どっちどっちどっち？
Which, which, which? Which, which, which?
どっちどっちどっち？どっち
Which, which, which? Which?
どっちどっちどっち？どっちどっち！？
Which, which, which? Which, which?!
んーどっちの君も大正解！
Hmm, either version of you is totally correct!
だってこの世はめちゃかわ世！
Because this world is super cute!
ダメなときもいいときもどっちもあるから会いに気づく
In bad times and good times, both exist, so we notice our love.
だいたいが大だいすきの結果
Mostly, it's the result of loving you so much!
ちょっとぐだぐだなさおりもうまく行かない一日も
Even on clumsy days or days nothing goes right,
生きてるだけでかわなのだ！でもかわ上の上にかわをつくる
Just being alive makes you cute! But let's create even more cuteness on top of cuteness!
だってこの世は鬼かわ世！完全なところこそかわ世！
Because this world is devilishly cute! Perfection itself is so cute!
生まれてくれてありがとね
Thank you for being born into this world.
みんな大だいだいだいすきでっ！
Everyone, I love you so much!
ねえねえもーっともーっと！
Hey hey, more and more!
かわよ！
Kawayo!
手を取りくれる君からもよ
Hands extended to you who gives me love,
あまねくに可愛いのよ創りましょ！！
I'll make the world around me Kawayo,
あまり振り回しすぎたら
Too much looking around and spinning,
ラヴって実はラヴなのだで
and I'll have love,
あまねくに可愛いのよ創りましょ！！
even though that's actually just love.
あまり振り回しすぎたら
Too much looking around and spinning,
もしかしてあきれられちゃうかな
you might just get sick of it, huh?
懲りずにね愛してほしいな
I want you to love me without holding back,
そんな言葉も言えないし
even though I can't even say that.
いつも器用にできないけど
I'm never as smooth as I'd like,
いつだって君が笑えるように頑張るので
but I'll try my hardest so that you can always smile,
愛してほしいな
so I want you to love me.
そんなところもかわよ！
Even parts like that are kawayo!
なんて世界がかわよ！
What a kawayo world!
今とかすべてがかわよ！
Right now, everything is kawayo!
ヨイヨイ！
Yoi yoi!
ヨイ！ヨイ！
まず朝起きたらチェック ザ 通知
First thing when I wake up, check notifications.
軽々未来コミュニケーション
Easy, future communication.
小粋なジョークでダンス ザ 通信
Smart joke to dance the transmission.
フロアを沸かせオヤユビで
Rock the floor with my thumb.
そろそろ時間だ 外に出なきゃ
It's about time, I gotta get outside!
通るのはもちろん裏通り
Taking the backstreet, of course.
誰にも会わずにゴールインのハズが
I should reach my goal without meeting anyone,
まさかの気になるあの人が
but unexpectedly, that person I care about says...
おはよう！
"Good morning!"
「エッ！？エト…ナンドコニ、イルノデスカー！？アノ今日ソノ…」
"Wait, what are you doing here?! Today, that's..."
「ドウシタノ！」
"What's wrong?"
「イヤ…イエ、アノ、チョット…ドウW イヤ！アノ、I、E、I?…」
"N-no, um, just... wh-w-what? Uh, I, E, I...?"
「うっわあああ！」
"Uwahhh!"
デ、デ、ディスコミュニケーション
Dis-dis-discommunication,
あなたと電波交信
wireless contact with you.
まるでできない 言葉が出ない
I just can't do it, words won't come out.
ちゅ、ちゅ、宙に舞っちゃうくらい
Floating away into the air.
フィーリングで通じ合いたい
With that feeling, I want to connect.
マジでできない 伝わりゃしない
I really can't do it, it just won't get across.
星の数の言葉の中から ひとつ何かを探してる
Searching for one thing among words like stars.
伝えたいのに しかしあたいは
I want to tell you, but I am...
ディスコミュ星人ダ！ダ！ダ！プー！
a discommunication alien! Da! Da! Da! Foo!
マイワールドならマイペースで思い通り(YEAH)
In my world, everything goes as I want (Yeah).
先手必勝 IN THE GOOD SHOW みたいな
First to act wins in the good show.
絶対負けない メゲない ショゲない 弱音は儚い
I won't lose, I won't give up, whining is momentary.
スポットライトでキラキラ輝く キラッと言いこなあたし
Shining bright in the spotlight, that's me☆
1.2.3.4.5.6.7.8.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
アドレナリン空回りだったり それでも笑顔でキュルキュルリン
Spinning from adrenaline, but still smiling, kyurukyururin.
プリンセスでいいんです それしか似合わないんです
I'm fine with being a princess, nothing else suits me.
目をみてしまえばみんな一撃からさういうお年頃
Once I look into their eyes, everyone's one-hit KO.
「え！急にみんなどうしたの！アリガト」
"Eh! What's with everyone all of a sudden? Thanks!"
「いやあ、そんなこと言われても照れるというかナントイカ(笑)」
"No, even if you say that, I feel shy or whatever (lol)."
「愛してる！」
"We love you!"
「え！？いや～困ったな(笑)」
"Eh?! Oh no, I'm in trouble (lol)."
「ありがとう嬉しいな、私も…」あ、夢か。
"Thank you, I'm so happy, me too..." Oh, it was a dream.
デ、デ、ディスコミュニケーション
Dis-dis-discommunication,
あなたの感情予想
predicting your feelings.
まるでできない 答えが出ない
I just can't do it, my response doesn't come out.
ちゅ、ちゅ、ちゅーじゃ足りないくらい
Chu, chu, chu-like it's not enough,
フィーリングで感じあって
feeling and understanding each other,
そのまま溶けて… とか、そんな妄想中
melting together just like that... or, that kind of daydream.
デ、デ、ディスコミュニケーション
Dis-dis-discommunication,
解答例的なナレーション
sample answer-like narration.
ガチでできない 伝わりゃしない
I truly can't do it, it just won't get across.
夢の中なら上手できるの だけどリアルじゃできやしない
If it's in a dream I can do it well, but in real life I just can't.
伝えたいほどキョドる心は おんなじ言語じゃないみたいなら
My strangely acting heart doesn't seem to be speaking the same language.
星の数の言葉は捨てるよ！
I'll throw away words as numerous as the stars!
気持ちはほら、ここにあるよ！ 伝えてみるさ だってあたいは
Look, here are my feelings, I'll try to tell you, because I am...
ディスコミュ星人ダ！ダ！ダ！…なんでもないです。
a discommunication alien! (It's nothing, really.)
ということで、みなさん今日来てくれてありがとうございます！
So, everyone, thank you so much for coming today!
1曲目は、Yoroの一番最新のオリジナル曲「かわよ」でした！
The first song was Yoro's latest original song, "Kawayo."
どうでしたか？
How was it?
この「かわよ」ね、Fesで初披露した曲なんですけど、今回が2回目になります。
This was the second time performing "Kawayo," which was unveiled at Fes.
どうだったかな、「かわよ」でしたか？
How was it? Was it "kawayo"?
かね、皆さん愛の手してくれましたかー！
Thank you for calling me Ai no Te.
そしてそして2曲目は「ディスコミュステーション」！
And then the second song is Disco Mutation!
いや元々ディスコミュステーションをめちゃ好きだったんですけど
Originally, I really loved Disco Mutation,
もうこの曲ちょっと難しかったですね。
but this song was quite difficult.
ちょっとあの途中のあのセリフがめちゃくちゃ噛みそうになりまして
The middle part of the lyrics was really breathless,
特にあの「1、2、3、4、5、6、7、8」のところがちょっとろれつが回らなそうな感じでちょっと焦ったんですけど
especially "1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8," which made me quite nervous.
ちょっとみなさんどうだったでしょうか！
So everyone, how was it?
というかね今回は誕生日ということでですね
Well then, since today is my birthday,
ステージがちょっと一新して可愛くなりましたー！
the stage was slightly renovated and became so cute!
見て見て！めっちゃかわいいでしょう！
Look, look! Isn't it super cute?
ちょっとこっち側を見てください。
Please look this way.
こっち側ね、でかいクマちゃんがいるんですよ。可愛いでしょう！
There's a huge bear over here, isn't it cute?
ちょっとねプレゼントもたくさんありまして、お誕生日仕様にしていただきました。
There are also many presents here for my birthday.
なんと反対側こっち側ですね、見てください！ぽよよんって！
And look, on the opposite side, look at this!
かわいい！ねえ、なんかケツジリボンもついてる！みたいな感じでですね
It looks like it's even wearing gyoza.
すごい可愛くしていただきました。お誕生日なんでね、
So cute, since it's my birthday,
もうめちゃめちゃ可愛いをたくさん詰めていただきました。
they packed lots of cute things for me!
そしてですね、みんなちょっと気づいたかな？
And did everyone notice?
ちょっとこのモニターのね、上を見てほしいんですけど！
Look at the top of the monitor!
見て！鬼の角がついているんです！可愛い！
It has horns, how cute!
見て上にもね、可愛いバルーンたちがたくさんついてるんですけどね、めっちゃ可愛いでしょう！今回ね、作っていただきました。ありがとうございます！
And there are cute balloons at the top too. Thank you for making this for me!
そして今回のライブはですね、え、ハッシュタグ、え、百鬼あやめ生誕祭2023となっておりますので、ぜひみなさんハッシュタグつけて、え、ステージやらダンスやら、よーのことやら、えーたくさんポストしてくれたら嬉しいなと思います。
And for today's live, the hashtag is #NakiriAyameBirthday2023, so please use the hashtag to post about the stage, dancing, and everything else!
この後ですね、ゲストがたくさん登場しますので、
After this, many guests will appear,
え、一緒にね、歌って踊っていくので、ぜひみなさんスクショやら撮ってくださいね！
so let's sing and dance together! Please take lots of screenshots!
というわけで、この後も見てねー！
So, let's keep watching after this too!
ありえない幻想
An impossible illusion,
あふれだす妄想
overflowing illusion,
君以外全部いらないわ
I don't need anything except you.
息をするように嘘ついても
Telling lies as if it were breathing,
あたしやっぱいらない子？
I don't need a fake me.
こぼれ出しちゃった承認欲求
Spilling out, my validation desire.
もっとココロ満たしてよ
Fill my heart even more.
アスパルテーム甘い夢
Aspartame, a sweet dream.
あたしだけに愛をください
Give me your love only.
もう無理マジ無理
No way, seriously no way.
恋して愛して救済執行ban☆
Fall in love, love, and get exorcised, ban!
ねー好きって言ってよ？
Hey, say you love me!
ありえない幻想
An impossible illusion,
あふれだす妄想
overflowing illusion,
とまんないつまんない
Unstoppable, boring.
欲が散らばって
Desires are scattering around.
求めてる愛情隠してる劣情
Hiding the affection I'm seeking,
君以外全部いらないわ
I don't need anything except you.
yeah
誰のこと見てんの？
Who are you looking at?
こういうの好きなの？
Do you like this kind of thing?
DDとかガチでやめてください
Please stop being a DD and be serious.
かわいくなりたい！
I want to be cute,
キラキラしてたい！
I want to sparkle,
もっともっとガチで褒めてください
Praise me even more seriously.
泣いちゃうちゃう
I might cry,
空けちゃうシャンパン
Champagne overflows.
今夜も配信来てくれるよね？
You'll come to my stream tonight too, right?
独占させてよ
Let me monopolize you.
本命なんでしょ？
Aren't you my oshi?
もっともっとガチで推してください
Support me even more seriously.
飲みすぎ注意オーバードーズ
Drinking too much caution, overdose.
クラクラさせていつでもさせて
Let's make it dizzy anytime.
もう無理マジ無理
No way, seriously no way.
アガってサガって救済執行ban☆
Rise and fall, get exorcised, ban!
ねー好きって言わせて？
Hey, let me say I love you!
噛みついた衝動
Biting impulse,
戻れない焦燥とまんないみたいな
Unstoppable impatience.
指が絡まって
Fingers intertwining,
ときめいた表情何も言わないで
Fluttering facial expression, don't say a word.
君だけがきっと王子様
You are my only prince.
ありえない幻想
An impossible illusion,
あふれだす妄想
overflowing illusion,
とまんないつまんない
Unstoppable, boring.
欲が散らばって
Desires are scattering around.
求めてる愛情隠してる劣情
Hiding the affection I'm seeking,
君以外全部いらないわ
I don't need anything except you.
あたしだけずっと追いかけて！
Just keep chasing only me!
ねーもう待てないの
Hey, I can't wait anymore!
君以外全部いらないわ
I don't need anything except you.
罰点採ったら頽れ顔
After getting a bad score, you grimace,
私はそんな貴方も素敵に見えるわ
and yet you still look so charming to me.
奇奇怪起きた夏の戯れに
In the bizarre pranks of a summer day,
もしやのもしや貴方に近づく好機か
could this just be my chance to get close to you?
ねぇ… どきりとしてしまうでしょ?
Hey... Doesn't your heart skip a beat?
もう純情ぶって偽っちゃって好き好き絶頂症
Feigning purity and pretending—love climax!
溶けちゃう前にさあ
Before it all melts away,
貴方が頬張って噂になって強がっちゃって
You puff out your cheeks and act all tough,
もう妄想絶好調 呼び捨てにしてよ
Delusions at their peak, just call me by name!
合点いかんの蒸した夜
A steamy, baffling night,
眠れず明くる朝まで貴方をひたすら
Sleeplessly thinking of you until the dawn,
すってんころり滑稽に
Comically slipping and falling flat,
紳士に助けられたくて淑女を被る
Wanting a gentleman to save me like a lady.
ねぇ… あの娘を見ないで
Hey... Don't look at that girl over there.
もう考えたって抗ったって好き好き絶頂症
Thinking and fighting it are useless—love climax!
べたべたしちゃうからもっと欲張って
We get so clingy, so let's be greedier,
恋愛成就に奢ったってもうそうどっちっち?
Acting arrogant about love, which way is it?
すれ違う貴方 目が眩んだ私
You passing by, and me, blinded by you.
みるく味のとけたあいす
Milky-flavored melted ice cream,
熱くなり赤くなって手の平と顔
Palms and face growing hot and red,
垂れる垂れるぽたり落ちる
Dripping, dripping, dropping heavily,
指伝い腕伝い甘い味
Down my fingers, down my arms, a sweet taste.
もう純情ぶって偽っちゃって好き好き絶頂症
Feigning purity and pretending—love climax!
溶けちゃう前にさあ
Before it all melts away,
貴方が頬張って噂を聞いたどうやら本当ずきずき痛いんだ
Hearing the rumors, it really throbs and hurts!
ねぇ… 鳴り止んで
Hey... Please stop.
鳴り止んで…
Please stop...
こころから、あい、へい、ちゅっちゅっちゅ！
From the bottom of my heart, I love you!
ベイビーあいへいちゅー
Baby, I love you!
ねぇはっきり言うけどベイビー 私なにからなにまであなたがノーセンキュー
Hey, to be honest baby, I'm into everything about you!
あい、へい、ちゅっちゅ！
Hey! Chu-chu!
ねぇ距離が近いほどベイビー 見えてくるくる気になるところの大発見
Hey, the closer we are, the more I discover about you!
ほのぼのしてるこのお部屋で 平穏はバイバイ
In this cozy room, peace is nowhere to be found!
おんなじ世界じゃやってけない！
We can't survive in the same world!
言ってるあれこれ通じてる！？ なにからなにまで分かってよ！
Are you getting my hints!? Understand everything about me!
あなたかなんともういいや とはいかない毎晩考えて
I can't just brush you off, thinking about it every night!
もうベイビーベイビーあい
Oh, baby, baby, love...
へい ちゅー へい ちゅー 心から あい へい ちゅっ ちゅっ ちゅ
Hey chu, hey chu, with all my heart, I hate chu-chu-chu!
ねえ はっきり 言う けど ベイビー
I'm telling you clearly, baby,
あたし 何から何まで あなた が ノー・サンキュー
you're a total no-thank-you from start to finish!
ああ 距離 が 近い ほど ベイビー
Ah, the closer the distance, baby,
見えてくるくる 気 に なる ところ の 大 バーゲン
coming into view, a big bargain of things I care about!
ほのぼのしてる この お部屋 で 平和 は バイバイ
Peaceful bye-bye in this cozy room!
おんなじ 世界 じゃ やって いけない！
We can't survive in the same world!
言って る アレコレ 通じてる！？
Are all those things I say getting across!?
なにか ら なに まで わかって よ！
Understand everything from start to finish!
あなた なんか もう いいや...
You're already enough...
…… と は いかない 毎晩 考え てる
...That's not how it goes, I think about it every night.
もう ベイビー ベイビー
More baby, baby,
あい へい ちゅー が とまらない！
my "I hate chu" won't stop!
これから さあ あなた と 何回 やん の
From now on, how many rounds of conversation
会話 の ドッジボール
will we play like dodgeball?
ベイビー ベイビー
Baby, baby,
アイニー ジー な レベル で あい へい ちゅー
at an easy-peasy level, I hate chu!
ウラ の ウラ の オモテ の ハート わかって ほしい ん だ よ
I want you to understand the heart behind the back and front!
もっと 見 て くれ なきゃ あい へい ちゅー！
If you don't look at me more, I hate chu!
気 に し て くれ なきゃ あい へい ちゅー！
If you don't care about me, I hate chu!
今日 こそ あなた に 伝え なきゃ
Today I really have to tell you,
やっぱ たまに 素直 が 一番 だ もん
after all, sometimes honesty is best!
今 まで 冷たく し て た 訳 じゃ ない よ？
It's not like I've been acting cold until now, right?
誤解 解き たい の 気づい て！
Notice that I want to clear up the misunderstanding!
じゃ ない と 知ら ない とこ に 行っちゃう よ？
Otherwise I'll go somewhere you don't know!
あのね あたし 実 は あなた の こと が...
You know, I actually... feel that way about you...
なんて 言えたら それ は もう 大成功！！
If I could say that, it's already a huge success!!
…… と は いかない 毎晩 反省 会
...That's not how it goes, debriefing every night.
ねえ ベイビー ベイビー
Hey baby, baby,
あい へい ちゅー が 終わら ない
my "I hate chu" won't end.
これ で また あなた と 何回 やっ た？
How many times did I do this with you again?
「もう バイバイ」 の チキン レース
"See you later" chicken race.
ヘイト ミー ヘイト ミー な ほど 離れ られ ない
So hate me, hate me, we can't pull apart.
キライ の ウラ に くっつく ハート わかって ほしい
I want you to understand the heart clinging behind hate.
おおー！ ベイビー ベイビー
Oh! Baby, baby,
あい へい ちゅー じゃ とまれ ない！
my "I hate chu" can't be stopped!
この まま さあ！ あなた と 何回 だって
Like this, how many times with you
愛 と ヘイト の シーソー ゲーム
a seesaw game of love and hate again and again!
ベイビー ベイビー
Baby, baby,
アイラブユー くらい 言わ せろ よ あい へい ちゅー！
Let me at least say I love you, I hate chu!
ウラ の ウラ じゃ 伝わらない の わかっ て いる から
Because I know that feelings won't get across behind the scenes,
それでも ヘイト 向け ちゃう アイ に 気づい て ほしい の
I still want you to notice the love turning into hate!
もっと 見 て くれ なきゃ あい へい ちゅー！
If you don't look at me more, I hate chu!
気 に し て くれ なきゃ あい へい ちゅー！
If you don't care about me, I hate chu!
もっと 見 て くれ なきゃ あい へい ちゅー！
If you don't look at me more, I hate chu!
気 に し て くれ なきゃ あい へい ちゅー！
If you don't care about me, I hate chu!
へい ちゅー へい ちゅー 明日 から あい へい ちゅっ ちゅっ ちゅ
Hey chu, hey chu, from tomorrow I hate chu-chu-chu!
えぶしー忘れてましたー！
I completely forgot the ABCs!
ということでみなさんどうだったでしょうか！
So everyone, how was that?
ゲストの一曲目は「妄想アスパルテーム」でした！
Our guest's first song was "Mousou Aspartame"!
そっちのね、あくあと初めて二人で
That's right, Aqua and I sang together
歌ったんですよ！すいちゃんライブで、あ、ありがとう！
for the very first time at Suichan's live! Ah, thank you!
いや妄想アスパルテームでめっちょいあくあの歌っててかわいくて「一緒に歌いたいな」と思って今回一緒に歌わせていただきました！
I love Aqua's cover of "Mousou Aspartame" so much, she's so cute, and I thought "I want to sing it together," so we got to sing it together this time!
そしてソロのは好き好き絶頂症、ちょっとあんまりなんかっぽくないからちょっと不安だったんですけど
And my solo was "Sukisuki Zecchousou." I was a bit worried because it didn't really seem like my style, but...
どうですか？どうですか？あ、かわいい、ありがとう！
how is it? How was it? Ah, cute? Thank you!
そしてそして三人ベイビーあいへいちゅーでね、ちとことねで歌いましたー！どうですかー！
And then the three of us sang "Baby Aiheichu" with Chito and Kone! How was it?
かわいいかったでしょー！そして、みんなお気づきになられました？
Wasn't it cute?! And did everyone notice?
あの夜の、この右手で持ってる、左手ですね、持ってるこのメガホンめちゃくちゃかわいいでしょ、見て！
This megaphone I'm holding in my right hand—ah, left hand, right? Look at this megaphone I'm holding, isn't it super cute?
今回のねライブのロゴが入っております、見えるかな？
It has our live concert logo on it. Can you see it?
そして、あ、これ、これ気づきました？ぽよよのチャームがついてるんです、やったー！
And, oh, did you notice this? It has a Poyoyo charm on it, yay!
いやこれ超かわいいでしょ、なんか、あのベビーあいへいちゅーのMVの中にメガホンと旗が出てくるんですけど
Isn't this super cute? In the MV for "Baby Aiheichu," a megaphone and a flag appear,
それをね、今回世論ステージ仕様に作っていただけましたー！ありがとうございます！
and they made this custom-designed for the Yoron stage! Thank you so much!
なんかね旗は、あの、用途確かかわいいよって書いてある大きい旗だったんですけど、あれはよが手描きで書いております！
As for the flag, it was supposed to be a big flag that says "kawaiiyo," and I hand-drew that myself!
見てくれたかな？もし見逃したたにんげん様はアーカイブでぜひ見てください！
Did you see it? If any humans missed it, please check the archive!
え、そしてですね、みんな気づいた？Tシャツもこれロゴ同じなんですよ、メガホンと。これかわいいでしょ、ロゴでめっちゃ可愛く作っていただけました！
And hey, did everyone notice? The T-shirt has the same logo as the megaphone. Isn't it cute? They made it look super cute with the logo, thank you!
Tシャツ着用 ちょっと、おなか出てるんですけど、ちょっと見ないでください（笑）
I'm wearing the T-shirt... my tummy is showing a bit, so please don't look haha!
そして、見て、ちょっと、かわいさ、ちょっと気づきましたみなさん？よいいつもブライト衣装スカートなんですよ、これ。
And look, isn't it cute? Did you guys notice? I'm always wearing a skirt in my Bright outfit,
いや、今日ね、パンツスタイルなんです！見てー！
but today, it's a pants style! Look!
かわいいですか？どうですかー？
Isn't it cute? What do you think?
そう、ちょっといつもスカート系なんで、ちょっと新鮮かなと思うんですけど
Yeah, since I usually wear skirts, I thought it'd be a nice change of pace,
ちょっとこのあとの曲中でもちょっとパンツスタイルが出てくるんじゃないかなって、お楽しみにね！
and maybe you'll see more pants style in the upcoming songs too, so look forward to it!
そしてそしてゲストもたくさん来ますので、お見逃しなく！見てねー！
And there are lots of guests coming too, so don't miss it! See ya!
僕が最高だから
Since I'm the best,
有名になる必要ないでしょ
I don't need to be famous, right?
今日も配信待ちきれないね
I can't wait for today's stream either!
この手紙を渡せば想いが伝わるかも！
If I hand over this letter, my feelings might get across!
まあ渡さないんだけどね！
Well, I'm not gonna hand it over though!
ちょっと待って！
Wait a minute!
知らないダメ
Not knowing is no good,
言わないダメ
not speaking is no good.
何々怪しいこととかないけど
Not that anything suspicious is going on, but...
言えないダメ
Not being able to say it is no good,
聞かないダメ
not listening is no good.
君のココロを教えてよ
Tell me your heart.
君の思わせぶりな態度でボクのココロは壊されてしまう
Your teasing attitude breaks my heart.
最低なんて言える柄でもないからもうわからない！
I'm not one to call myself the worst, so I don't get it anymore!
君は完璧だから有名になりたい
You're perfect, so you want to be famous,
だけどボクは猛反対
but I'm strictly against it!
ボクが最適になる運命で
It's my destiny to be your best match,
怒らせちゃダメだから完全防備で
so don't make me angry, fully prepared,
最低な思い出作ったって塗り替えてくれるよ何回も
even if we make the worst memories, you'll rewrite them time and time again!
僕が最高だから
Since I'm the best,
有名になる必要ないでしょ
I don't need to be famous, right?
今日の配信耐えきれないね
I can't bear today's stream either!
あの人あの人と付き合ってるらしいよ
I heard that person is dating someone,
配信者なのにいいの？
is that okay for a streamer?
もしかしたら私も！
Maybe I could too?!
ちょっと待って！
Wait a minute!
知らないダメ
Not knowing is no good,
何様なんて？
what do you mean 'who do I think I am'?
何々やましいこととかないけど
Not that there's anything guilty about it, but...
言えないダメ
Not being able to say it is no good,
やめたくないしダメ！
I don't want to stop, no good!
あなたのココロ教えてよねえ
Tell me your heart, hey...
君の笑顔でボクの心は癒されてゆくの
Your smile heals my heart.
最低なんて思えるはずもないからだけどわからない
I could never think of myself as the worst, but I don't understand.
僕は最低だから有名になりたい
Since I'm the worst, I want to be famous,
君を求める純愛者
a pure lover seeking you.
君の最適になる運命で諦めちゃダメだから
It's my destiny to be your best match, so don't give up!
完全勝利で最低な恋で終わったって
Even if it ends in total victory and the worst romance,
メルカリで買えるよ何回も
you can buy it on Mercari over and over!
僕が安定だから
Since I'm stable,
有名になる必要ないでしょ
I don't need to be famous, right?
今日も配信待ちきれない
I can't wait for today's stream!
ああ恋人じゃないのにあれこれ言われるでもないのに
Ah, even though we're not lovers, even though people aren't saying this or that,
この胸のドキドキは何なのだ？
what is this pounding in my chest?
ああなんてね
Ah, just kidding!
君は完璧だから有名になりたい
You're perfect, so you want to be famous,
だけどボクは猛反対
but I'm strictly against it!
ボクが最適になる運命で
It's my destiny to be your best match,
怒らせちゃダメだから完全防備で
so don't make me angry, fully prepared,
最低な思い出作ったって塗り替えてくれるよ何回も
even if we make the worst memories, you'll rewrite them time and time again!
僕が最高だから
Since I'm the best,
有名になる必要ないでしょ
I don't need to be famous, right?
今日も配信耐えきれない
I can't bear today's stream!
ねぇ、チューして？
Hey, kiss me?
チュー、こっそり撮りたいな
I want to secretly record a kiss,
ネットで炎上しちゃうかな
will it cause online backlash, I wonder?
有名になった時彼氏がいたらやばいかな
If I had a boyfriend after becoming famous, would that be bad?
綺麗に生きてなきゃ
If I don't live purely,
応援してもらえないのかな
will people stop supporting me?
黒歴史上等な私じゃちょっとヤバイかな
With someone like me who embraces a dark past, is that a bit dangerous?
十字架背負う覚悟がないのなら
If you don't have the resolve to carry the cross,
その夢私にくれよ
give that dream to me!
生き急いでるわかってんだよ
I know I'm living in a rush,
だって今の私は今消えちゃう
because the me of right now is going to disappear.
ああ、あいどんきるゆー
Ah, I don't care you—
アイドルになって君のこと好きになりすぎたのは私の方なの
Becoming an idol and falling way too in love with you is on my side!
会いに来て、会いたい！
Come see me, I want to see you!
ああ、あいどんきるゆーアイコン変えてよ
Ah, I don't care you— change your icon!
どんな私がキャッチーよ
What kind of me is catchy?
胸元その先のびびたる乙女を見てね
Look at the timid maiden beyond my chest,
愛してる、チュープリンセス
I love you, Chuu Princess!
気づいていたの
You noticed,
私の名前のTシャツの下に
beneath the T-shirt with my name,
透けてるあの子の文字
the letters of that girl showing through...
チュープリ撮りたいな
I want to take a purikura...
ネットで炎上しちゃう かな
Will I end up getting cancelled on net?
有名になったとき
When I become famous,
彼氏がいたらヤバいかな
would it be bad if I have a boyfriend?
きれいに生きてなきゃ
I've gotta live pretty,
応援してもらえないのかな
or can't I even get some support?
黒歴史上等な私じゃちょっとヤバいかな
Am I the type with a black history?
十字架背負う覚悟がないのかなって
Don't I have the resolve to carry a cross?
お手軽に好きになっていいよ
Then just let me be casually fond of you!
私生活とか色々あって
I've got all sorts in my personal life,
だって今は私で幸せでしょ
'cause right now, I'm happy being me!
はぁーん…
Haaahn...
あ ああ あいどんきるゆー
Ah, ah, ah, idol kill you!
年の離れる君でも
Even if you're older than me,
どこかは私に似てる
somewhere you're just like me.
なんでなんか許せないこととかあったとしても
Even if there are things I can never forgive,
あ ああ あいどんきるゆー
Ah, ah, ah, idol kill you!
ぜんぶ好きだよ
I love all of it!
君が君であるディティールのひとつに私が立っていられたら
To be able to stand right beside every single detail
that makes you who you are,
それはなんという…！
what do you call that...?
チュープリンセス chu!
Chu Princess! Chu!
ねぇ、私の可愛いとこ100回言って！
Hey, tell me I'm cute 100 times!
う〜可愛いですね、黙って！
"Ugh, you're cute, okay? Shut up!"
顔、髪、肌、あと何？
Face, hair, skin, what else?
あ〜おっぱいおっぱい！
"A-Boobs, boobs!"
いつでも1番可愛いよ〜
I'm always the cutest, you know?
あ〜でもぶっちゃけ知ってるから、
Ah, but truthfully, I know—
自分でも可愛いと思えないとこ君に好きでいてほしいんだな！
I want you to love even the parts of me
ねぇ、もっとちゅーしてよ！
Hey, give me more chuu!
あ ああ あいどんきるゆー
Ah, ah, ah, idol kill you!
アイドルになって
Becoming an idol,
君のこと好きになりすぎたのは私の方なの
I fell way too deeply in love with you.
会いに来て！
Come meet me!
あ ああ あいどんきるゆー
Ah, ah, ah, idol kill you!
アイコン変えよー どんな私がキャッチーよ
Change your icon! Catch whatever kind of me—
でねもっとその先の微々たる乙女をみてね
Look at this tiny maiden way beyond that!
愛してる
I love you!
チュープリンセス chu!
Chu Princess! Chu!
We are スティーレ！！
We are Stîle!!
さあ扉を開けて 未知なるパラダイス
Open the door and let's experience
体験しよう
an unknown paradise!
おいで おいでYOU
Come on, come on, YOU!
キミを待つのは 不思議なオアシス
What awaits you is a mysterious oasis.
ほっこり日常に ちょっぴりSpice
A cozy daily life with a little spice,
かきまぜちゃうんだ
stirring it all around!
当店自慢のフレーバー
Our shop's pride and joy flavor!
サービス サービスご褒美タイム
Service, service, reward time!
おもてなし ココロこめて
Putting our hearts into our hospitality,
Welcome to... わたし達と一緒に
welcome to our shop!
めくるめくワンダーデイドリーム
A whirling, turning wonderland!
愛情マシマシ 煩悩ナデナデ
Overflowing affection, reluctant worries,
誠心誠意つとめます
we serve you with all our heart and soul!
いえーす！ キミの元気チャージにひと役かえるかな
Yes! Can we play a part in recharging your energy?
こーいった感じも あーいった感じも
An attitude like this, an attitude like that,
意外と悪くないでしょ？
isn't actually half bad, is it?
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono, Buono, we want to blend!
キミにきゅんきゅんきゅん ハートにぱんぱんぱん
Right into your heart, kyun kyun kyun, bang bang bang!
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono, Buono, we want to blend!
お口にあいますか？
Does this suit your tastes?
お口にあうといいな♪
We hope it hits the spot♪
千客ばんぱーんーい！
Welcome, honored guests!
ちょっと、なんか、不本意ながらも
Well, even though we might be reluctant,
いつだって需要は斜め上
demand is always skewed upward!
ぼなぺてぃーと
Bon appétit!
そんじゃ、いっか、ホントのわたしは
So anyway, the real me is...
シークレットモードで営業スイッチオン
secret mode, business switch ON!
ぐるんぐるん かきまぜてもっと
Stirring it all around,
キミ仕様のフレーバー
your custom flavor!
サービス サービス極上タイム
Service, service, supreme time!
癒しとはかくあるべき
True healing should be like this!
Welcome to... わたし達のお店に
Welcome to our shop,
本日もようこそ
welcome back today as well!
おかえり待ってた リピートうれしいな
We've been waiting for you to come home—
店員一同歓迎 いえーす！
the entire staff welcomes you once again!
キミのお疲れ様にピッタリのレシピで
With the perfect recipe for your hard work,
こーゆーのどーかな
I wonder if this feels right,
あーゆーのありかな
I wonder if this is okay,
よろこんでもらえてるかな
I wonder if you'll gladly accept it!
Smile・Sweet・Sister・Sadistic
Smile, Sweet, Sister, Sadistic
Surprise・Service・We are スティーレ！！
Surprise, Service, We are Stile!!
さあ 扉を開けて
Come open the door,
未知なるパラダイス
a mysterious paradise.
体験しよう おいで おいでYOU
Let's experience it, come on, come on YOU!
そう キミを待つのは 不思議なオアシス
Yes, what awaits you is a mysterious oasis,
ほっこり日常に ちょっとSpice
a cozy daily life with a little spice.
くーるん くーるん かきまぜちゃうぞ
Spinning round and round, stirring it up,
ぐーるん ぐーるん 当店自慢のフレーバー
our shop's proud flavor rolling round and round.
サービス サービス ご褒美タイム
Service, service, reward time,
おもてなし ココロこめて
hospitality packed with heart.
Welcome to...
わーい！ 私達と一緒にめくるめくワンダデイリーム
Yay! A dazzling wonder day dream together with us.
愛情マシマシ 煩悩ナデナデ 誠心誠意つとめます
Affection extra, serving with all our heart.
いえーす！ キミの元気チャージにひと役かえるかな
Yes! Can I play a part in recharging your energy?
こーいった感じも あーいった感じも 意外と悪くないでしょ？
Doesn't this kind of feeling turn out surprisingly not bad?
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono Buono, I want to blend.
キミにきゅんきゅんきゅん ハートにぱんちぱんちぱんち
Kyun kyun to you, punch punch to your heart!
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono Buono, I want to blend.
お口にあいますか？ お好み聞かせてね
Does it suit your taste? Let me know your preference.
お口にあうといいな♪
I hope it suits your taste♪
鏡よ鏡よ鏡さん
Mr. mirror, Mr. mirror, there on the wall,
世界で一番可愛いのは
please stop telling me I am the fairest of all.
鏡よ鏡よ鏡さん
Mr. mirror, Mr. mirror, there on the wall,
世界で一番可愛いがるのは やめてよ 棘のような視線迫る
stop telling me I am the fairest as jealous stares bear down.
優しいふりした彼女が 素敵な晩餐もてなした そっと口に含む「笑い」
She was so kind, made me a meal, then she laughed.
息絶えてゆく
As my vision fades to black...
夢を見てる いつのおとぎ話
I dream about a fairytale; time has frozen.
お願いKISSで目を覚まして欲しいの
Please, I beg you, wake me up with a kiss of true love.
白い棺から 連れ出すように
Carry me away from this white coffin.
突き刺さる憎しみは ドラマ的な事情
Jealousy is such a tragic, dramatic feeling.
祈っても 王子様はまだ来ない
Yet no matter what, my prince charming is still not here.
鏡よ鏡よ鏡さん
Mr. mirror, Mr. mirror, what do I do?
ネクタイ任せや頬に挨拶するから 妬みをかわれてしまった
If I fix your necktie, I can feel their envy start to break through.
7人の小人はいるけど 助ける素振り、知らん振りね 首を捕まえ「笑い」一粒の涙さえ拭えなくて 呼吸もままならない
Hands on my throat, unable to dry my tears or breathe.
消えそうだから 早く駆けて欲しいの
I am running out of time, hurry soon before I leave.
訳は聞かないで 応えられない 望まない憎まれは 深い愛の二乗
Please don't ask why; unwanted hatred is deep love squared.
消えそうだから 早く駆けて欲しいの
I am running out of time, hurry soon before I leave.
訳は聞かないで 応えられない
Please don't ask me why because I cannot answer.
望まない憎まれは 深い愛の二乗 もうすぐでなくなるのかな
Unwanted hatred is deep love squared. Will I disappear soon?
途切れてく命の音 毒リンゴを食した少女のように眠りにつく
Breathing slow like a maiden who ingested a poison red apple.
お願いKISSで目を覚まして欲しいの
Wake me up with a kiss, please.
胸の中の声届きますか
Can you hear my heart beating so?
階段を上ったら ドアをあけるだけで
Climb up the stairs and open up the door.
見つかるよ
find me...
あぁ
Ah...
お 願い K I S S で 目 を 覚 ま し て 欲 し い の
Please wake me up with a kiss,
白 い 棺 か ら 連 れ 出 す よ う に
so you can lead me out of this white coffin.
突 き 刺 さ る 憎 し み は ド ラ マ 的 な 事 情 祈 っ て も 王 子 様 は ま だ 来 な い
Even if I pray, my prince charming still hasn't come...
消 え て し ま う
Before I fade away...
そ の 前 に ‥ ‥
before that...
わざとあざとエキスパート
Wazato Azato Expert
なんでいつもそっけないのよ
Why are you always so distant?
クール気取っちゃって
Playing it cool?
会いたいんでしょ？
Want to see me?
恋しいんでしょ？
In love with me?
素直になろうよ！
Let's be honest!
それなら君の気を引いちゃいます
That'll surely catch your eye!
ドキドキ溢れる大作戦
A heart-throbbing grand strategy!
1分 2分 3分 4分 LINEも未読スルーするんだ
1 min, 2 min, 3 min, 4 min, left on "unread" on LINE...
「最近なんだか気になって仕方ないんだよな…」
"Lately, I can't help but think about you..."
そんな感じで毎晩ずっと
With feelings like that every single night,
何度も何度もきっと SNSチェックしちゃうでしょ？
I'm checking your SNS over and over again!
ほら、もっと夢中になって！
Hey, get more captivated!
わざと上げたこのストーリー 君の足跡チェックするの
Checking your footsteps on this story I posted on purpose.
あざといなんて言わないで
Don't you dare call me manipulative!
だって Love you love you love you 好きだっちゃ！はい！
Because it's love you, love you, love you, "I love you!" Yes!
わざと遅い既読通知 私の心非公開
On-purpose late "Read" receipts, my private heart,
鍵をかけた恋心 ねぇほらほらほら
a locked-up romance, hey, come on, come on!
私を気にして もっともっと
Pay more attention to me, more and more!
私の声で君が笑うから
Because my voice makes you smile,
その瞬間も切り取って即保存しちゃいたい
I want to capture that very moment and save it instantly!
そのために心奪っちゃいます 明日は君の誕生日
I'm gonna steal your heart for that! Tomorrow is your birthday!
5分 4分 3分 2分 「おめでとう！」わざと早まって
5 min, 4 min, 3 min, 2 min... "Happy Birthday!" I was early on purpose
「ごめん、誰より早く伝えたかったんだ」
"Sorry, I just wanted to tell you before anyone else."
そんなこと言えばあっという間
Speaking of which, in a split second,
チョコレートみたい溶けちゃうね
it melts away like chocolate!
もう！早くこっち向いて！
Hey, turn this way already!
わざとあざとエキスパート 私の心覗いてよ
Wazato Azato Expert, let me peek into your heart!
タイムラインは君ばっかり Love you love you love you
Your timeline is all about me, love you, love you, love you!
ドキドキきゅん！チュッ 君だけに限定公開
Dokidoki kyun! Chu! Exclusive to you!
足跡つくの待ってるのに このままいけばログアウト
I'm waiting for your footprints, but if this keeps up, I'll log out!
やだ！やだ！やだ！私を愛して ずっとずっと
No way, no way, no way! Love me forever and ever!
やっと見れた君のアカウント
I finally got to see your account!
やっぱ君も私のこと好きなんだね
I guess you like me too, huh?
わざとは全部君のためなんだから
All of this "manipulative" stuff is just for you,
落ちちゃえばいいんだ
so falling for it is fine!
だけど私少し反省
Though I'm feeling a little bit regretful,
あまり試すの良くないね
testing you this much isn't good, huh?
やけに遅い既読通知 やっぱ気になる！なる！なる！
On-purpose late "Read" receipts, I'm starting to care!
わざと上げたこのストーリー 君の足跡チェックするの
Checking your footsteps on this story I posted on purpose.
あざといなんて言わないで
Don't you dare call me manipulative!
やっぱ Love you love you love you 好きだっちゃ！はい！
Because it's love you, love you, love you, "I love you!" Yes!
わざと遅い既読通知 私の心非公開
On-purpose late "Read" receipts, my private heart,
鍵をかけた恋心 ねぇほらほらほら
a locked-up romance, hey, come on, come on!
私を気にして もっともっと まさか君もわざとなの？
Pay more attention to me, more and more! Could it be you're doing it on purpose too?
なんで いつも そっけない の よ ！？
Why are you always so cold to me?!
クール 気取っ ちゃって
Acting all cool...
会い たい でしょ ？ 恋しい でしょ ？
Don't you want to see me? Miss me?
素直 に なろ う よ ！
Let's be honest!
それなら 君 の 気 を 引い ちゃい ます
In that case, I'll grab your attention!
ドキドキ 溢れる 大作戦
A heart-throbbing grand strategy!
1分 2分 3分 4分 LINEも未読スルーするんだ
1 min, 2 min, 3 min, 4 min, leaving my LINE unread!
「最近なんだか気になって仕方ないんだよなー」
"Lately, I can't help but think about you all the time—"
そんな感じで毎晩ずーーっと何度も何度もきっと
Every single night, endlessly, over and over, I'm sure
SNSチェックしちゃうでしょ？
you check my SNS, right?
ほら！もっと夢中になって！
Hey! Get even more obsessed!
わざとあげた このストーリー
This story I posted on purpose,
君の足跡チェックするの
checking for your footprints—
「あざとい」なんて言わないでだって
Don't call it "calculated," because
love you, love you, love you, 好きだっちゅ！はいっ！
love you, love you, love you, I love you! Yes!
わざと遅い既読通知 私の心 非公開
Deliberately delayed read receipt, my heart is private
鍵をかけた恋心 ねぇほらほらほら
A locked-up romance, hey look, look, look,
私を気にしてもっともっと
pay more and more attention to me!
キス感あるよね
It has a kissing vibe, right?
去年もね、みんなに...
Last year too, everyone...
踊ってもらいましたね
danced to it!
踊って踊りました！
We danced and danced!
ちょっとあの... ドキドキしちゃって
I was getting all nervous...
ドキドキが... ね、みんな今年も...
My heart was racing... Everyone, this year too...
なんで呼んでくれたんですか？
Why did you invite us?
え、去年、ちょっと... 反響がよかった...
Well, last year, the response was so good...
ユニット化しちゃいます？
Should we turn into a unit?
いいんですか！？一緒に歌ってくれたってことですもんね！
Is that okay?! That means you'll sing with me!
そうそう！ 2回、3回目あるかどうかは
Exactly! Whether there's a 2nd or 3rd time...
ちょっと、までーもみんな次第！ みんな次第で、あれまではやる気ですよ！
Well, it all depends on everyone! Depending on everyone, we're motivated!
で、でもやっぱりほら、視聴者さんの...
But, but after all, look, the viewers'...
結果がすべてなんですか！？
Is the result everything?!
出さないと... ね、結果がすべて進むんですか！？
If we don't produce... right, does the result dictate everything?!
出さないと... 出さないとこのユニットは解散じゃ...
If we don't, if we don't, this unit will disband...
いやまずいまずいまずい！ちょっとみんな助けてください！
No, that's bad, bad, bad! Everyone, please help us!
でね、ほら、なんかほらユニットで... 名前とか決まってないと
And you know, in a unit, if you don't have a name decided...
応援しづらいよね そう応援しづらい
It's hard to support, right? Yeah, hard to support.
でさっきちょっとね、みんなで話してさ、ユニット名色々考えてね
So earlier we talked a bit and thought of various unit names,
そうなんです！やっぱりまず頭文字で...
That's right! First, with the initials...
の提案なんですけど... え、なんですか？なんですか？
is our proposal... Eh, what is it? What is it?
アムカラッペ...
Amu-Karappe...
アムカラに、はい。へ、田舎風の方じゃなくて
Amu-Kara, yes. Not the country-style one,
なんかの、ペチーノとかの
like... Peccino or something.
ペチーノみたいなやつです！ 可愛いやつ！なんか田舎...
Something like Peccino! A cute one! Like country...
大丈夫？ペドロって聞こえた... 大丈夫？
Are you okay? I heard Pedro... Are you okay?
ペチーノね！ペチーノ可愛いよね！集まった時はペチーノって呼ぼうじゃん！
Peccino! Peccino is cute! Let's call ourselves Peccino when we gather!
ペチーノの末裔！可愛い！
Descendants of Peccino! So cute!
ペチーノいいじゃん！いいじゃないですか！
Peccino is good! Isn't it good?!
他にも有有力なユニット名ありますか、ちなみに？
Are there any other strong unit contenders, by the way?
えーでもなんかね、みんなの、英語で... プ、フランクみたいな
Well, but you know, everyone's... in English... like, uh, Frank...
プロ、プロンクみたいな... 辛い、かっこいい感じの
Pro, Plonk-like... spicy, cool style...
クランプとかね！クランプも順序変えてね
Clump or something! Changing the order too,
でも今のところアムカラッペが一番頭に残る...
but right now Amu-Karappe sticks in our heads the most...
アナタラペもあります！ なっちゃうんでよかったら募集します
There's also Anata-Rape! Wait, it turns into that, so if you'd like, we're recruiting!
なんだそれ！ みんなはしゃいでるけどさ
What is that?! Everyone is getting all excited, but,
結果がすべてですよ、結果が！
the result is everything, the result!
結果が出さないならこのユニットは解散！
If we don't get results, this unit disbands!
いやまずいまずいまずい！ ちょっとみんな助けてください！
No, that's bad, bad, bad! Everyone, please help us!
みんな、アムカラッペを助けてください！ 切り抜いてみんな！
Everyone, please save Amu-Karappe! Clip this, everyone!
色んな収益化を... ゆかが... ゆかが潰れちゃう...
Various monetizations... Yuka... Yuka is going to collapse...
いや、あやめ先輩がクランプで... どうしちゃったの？
Wait, Ayame-senpai in Clump... What happened to you?
こんな疲れた体を癒すための、あれがあるんだって？
There's something to heal such an exhausted body, you say?
おっ？ なにがあるんですか？
Oh? What is there?
癒されたい時にはどこに行きたいの？
When you want to be healed, where do you want to go?
グッズが！ でます！
Merch! Is coming out!
なんだグッズ！ グッズが出る！やったー！
What, merch! Merch is coming out! Yay!
疲れたM先輩を癒す、そんなグッズは？
What kind of merch is there to heal the exhausted M-senpai?
ある！ そんなグッズはこちらです！ ドーン！
There is! That merch is right here! Ta-da!
誕生日記念フルセット2023！
Birthday Full Set 2023!
そしてこちら... B2タペストリー！
And this... B2 Tapestry!
えーこちら、音声、音声もテーマにしたですね、B2タペストリーが、えーこちら出まーす！やったー！
Um, this B2 tapestry, themed around voice as well, um, comes out here! Yay!
こちら、saino先生に描いていただきました！ありがとうございます！可愛い！
This was illustrated by saino-sensei! Thank you very much! So cute!
そしてそして、続きまして、ドーン！ ソープディスペンサーセット！
And then, continuing, ta-da! Soap dispenser set!
こちら3本をご用意しております！ 3本！ シャンプー、コンディショナー、ボディソープで3本です！
We have prepared 3 bottles for this! 3 bottles! Shampoo, conditioner, and body soap, 3 bottles!
こちら猫敷ふしお先生に描いていただきました！ありがとうございます！
This was illustrated by Neko Shiki Fushio-sensei! Thank you very much!
続きまして、ドーン！ お風呂おけ！
Continuing, ta-da! Bath basin!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
やったー！
Yay!
え、次は新ず…
And next up is...
どん！
Don!
こちら、お風呂マットも出まーす！
This is the bath mat!
いえーい！
Yay!
次はこちら、どん！
And next is... Don!
シチュエーションボイスが出まーす！
The situation voice is out!
今回は、「まったり夜桜温泉デート」となっておりまーす！
It's called "A Relaxing Late-Night Hot Spring Date"!
ちょっと恥ずかしいんですけど、
It's a bit embarrassing,
ぜひよかったら聞いてくださーい！
but please give it a listen if you'd like!
やったー！
Yay!
ということでですね、誕生日記念フルセットは、
So, the Birthday Commemorative Full Set includes...
直筆サイン入りポストカードと数量限定verは、直筆サイン入りポストカードとなっておりまーす！
a postcard with a handwritten signature and quantity-limited version!
やったー！
Yay!
どうしたの？
What happened?
あ、そう、数量、数量限定ボイスもさっきの…あ、ボイスは数量限定バージョンは、
And as for the voice, the quantity-limited version...
お風呂上がりの幸せな時間ということで…幸せな時間、
"A Relaxing Late-Night Hot Spring Date" voice,
フルセットのね、フルセットのね、はい、特別ボイス付いていきまーす！
which is a special voice for the full set!
幸せなのが大事！
Happiness is important!
あ、そう、さっき数量、数量限定バージョンは、直筆サインカードと、あ、サインカードがなくてなくなり次第、箔押し複製サインカードとなっておりまーす！
And the quantity-limited version includes a handwritten signature card and foil-stamped signature card!
よろしくお願いしまーす！
Thank you!
みんなね、あ、いいな、ありがとうございます！今日来てくれて、ね！
Thank you so much for joining today!
ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
ぜひ、来年もよろしくお願いします！
We hope you'll look forward to next year as well!
がんばりまーす！
Thank you so much!